roomstogo.com 2006-06-18

# Furniture Retailer - Home & Contemporary Online Furniture Shopping :: Rooms To Go :

Company : Privacy Statement

Privacy Statement

 **Roomstogo.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site: www.roomstogo.com. 

Registration

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and e-mail address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor during business hours for either customer service support or any order-processing questions we may have. The customer will also be contacted to confirm the delivery date and time. We also may use registration information to provide customers with opportunities to purchase other products or services that we believe may be of interest to them. Users may opt-out of receiving e-mail marketing communications; see the choice/opt-out section. Financial information that is collected is used to check the users' qualifications for registration and to bill the user for products and services. Unique identifiers are collected to verify the user's identity and for use as account numbers in our record system. 

Ordering / Purchasing

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitors' contact information (like their e-mail address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders to our customers. The customers' contact information is also used to contact the visitor during business hours for either customer service support or any order processing questions we may have. The customer will also be contacted to confirm the delivery date and time. We may use this information to provide customers with opportunities to purchase other products or services that we believe may be of interest to them. Users may opt-out of receiving future e-mail marketing communications; see the choice/opt-out section. Financial information that is collected is used to check the users' qualifications and bill the user for products and services. Unique identifiers are collected from web site visitors to verify the user's identity and for use as account numbers in our record system. 

Safeguarding Your Information

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Security enhancements were implemented to protect our most valuable asset, our customers. We have taken precautions and have invested in technology that will help keep your transaction safe. When you use the Rooms To Go Credit Card or another credit card to make a purchase at roomstogo.com, we use Secure Socket Layering (SSL) to encrypt your personal credit information, including your credit card number, before it travels over the Internet. SSL technology is the industry standard for secure online transactions. See the security section. 

Resume Submissions

Our site uses a form for vistors' to submit an online resume. We collect visitors' contact information (like their name, mailing address and e-mail address) and employment information (like employment eligibility, work experience and education). This information is submitted to Rooms To Go Human Resources Dept and is not used for any purpose other than in connection with the employment process. Rooms To Go currently does not accept applications online from applicants under 18 years of age. 

Choice / Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving e-mail marketing communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. See the choice/opt-out section. 

Correct And Update Your Information

We provide several different methods for you to change or modify the information you give us. See the correct and update section. 

Links To Other Sites

This site contains links to other sites. Rooms To Go is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. 

IP Address

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather demographic information. 

Use of Cookies

This site uses cookies, both "permanent and session". A "cookie" is a small data file stored by your web browser on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies allow us to recognize who you are when you arrive at our site by associating the identification numbers in the cookie with other information you as a customer have provided us. That customer information is stored on our secured database. Cookies allow us to understand how you clicked to our site and what pages you click on during your visit to our site. Knowing who you are and how you prefer to shop allows us to personalize your shopping experience and speed your checkout process. We do not use the cookie to track your activity on sites other than those operated by Rooms To Go. Accepting cookies through your web browser is your personal choice. You can still shop and purchase from roomstogo.com even if you set your browser to disable cookies. However, if you choose not to accept cookies, we will not be able to provide you with as exceptional a shopping experience as one that is specifically tailored to your needs. 

Notification of Changes

If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different in a material way from that stated at the time of collection we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post the notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. 

Other

We may share user information in the event that it is necessary to respond to any subpoena, court orders, or legal process. Moreover, we may share personally identifiable information to comply with legal requirements, to protect our rights and property or those of our users, to protect the safety of our sites or users, to enforce our Terms of Service, or in the event of a bankruptcy, or a merger, acquisition, joint venture, or other business combination involving us. 

Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, see the Contacting the Site section. 

_This privacy statement was updated on June 24, 2004._
